Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office. Media Center Audiovisual Collection, 1953-2015 and undated RL.00734
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office. Media Center Audiovisual collection
1953-2015 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office
RL.00734
60.0 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York. Collection includes correspondence, track listings, transcriptions, and other printed materials, audio and video cassettes (Betacam SP, VHS and Umatic), DAT, optical media (CDs, DVDs. etc.), 16mm film reels, phonograph records, and computer media. JWT management events documented in the collection include Cannes and Effies Awards submissions, Epcot, Executive Committee, Worldwide Creative Council, speeches and presentations by top managers as well as interviews undertaken as part of an oral history project at JWT. Offices represented include North America, Europe, Great Britain, India, Asia and Latin America. Main companies include California Lottery, Chase & Sanborn, Chevron, Del Taco, Diageo, Diamond Trading Company (DeBeers), Domino's, Ford, HSBC, Jenny Craig, JetBlue, Kaiser Permanente, Kimberly-Clark, Kodak, Kraft, Lipton, Macy's, Mexicana Airlines, Standard Brands, Trailways, Warner-Lambert, Weight Watchers and Wyeth. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Access Restrictions
Access restricted. Collection contains fragile audiovisual/photographic formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office. Media Center Audio-Visual Collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1993-2015.
Collection Overview
Collection includes correspondence, track listings, transcriptions, and other printed materials, audio and video cassettes (Betacam SP, VHS and Umatic), DAT, optical media (CDs, DVDs. etc.), 16mm film reels, phonograph records, and computer media. JWT management events documented in the collection include Cannes and Effies Awards submissions, Epcot, Executive Committee, Worldwide Creative Council, speeches and presentations by top managers as well as interviews undertaken as part of an oral history project at JWT. Offices represented include North America, Europe, Great Britain, India, Asia and Latin America. Main companies include California Lottery, Chase & Sanborn, Chevron, Del Taco, Diageo, Diamond Trading Company (DeBeers), Domino's, Ford, HSBC, Jenny Craig, JetBlue, Kaiser Permanente, Kimberly-Clark, Kodak, Kraft, Lipton, Macy's, Mexicana Airlines, Standard Brands, Trailways, Warner-Lambert, Weight Watchers and Wyeth. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising -- Pacific Area; Advertising -- Asia; Advertising -- United States; Videocassettes; Machine-readable records; Color slides; Radio advertising; Audiocassettes; Television advertising; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- India -- History; Advertising agencies -- Europe -- History; Advertising agencies -- Asia; Advertising agencies -- Latin America; Advertising agencies -- United States; J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Asia-Pacific Region; J. Walter Thompson Company. Argentina Office; Eastman Kodak Company; Weight Watchers International; Thomas J. Lipton, Inc.; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; J. Walter Thompson Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. San Francisco Office
- Documents and Supporting Materials, 1959-2003; undated; 1
  - Asia Pacific Creative Review, 2000 (Box 1)
  - JWT Japan, 1985 (Box 1)
  - RL00734-BETA-009: Korea (Box 1)
  - RL00734-BETA-010: London (Box 1)
  - RL00734-BETA-015: Paris (Box 1)
  - RL00734-BETA-027: Sydney (Box 1)
  - RL00734-CS-089: Crystal Ball (Box 1)
  - RL00734-CS-164: Mobilink (Box 1)
  - RL00734-DAT-001 through DAT-011 (Box 1)
  - RL00734-DAT-012 through DAT-028 (Box 1)
  - RL00734-DAT-030 through DAT-044 (Box 1)
  - RL00734-DAT-046 through DAT-060 (Box 1)
  - RL00734-DAT-061 through DAT-075 (Box 1)
  - RL00734-FL3-009: Nabisco Ritz 1999 Effie Submission (Box 1)
  - RL00734-OP-0015 through OP-0604 (Box 1)
  - RL00734-OP-0010; UMATIC-019: Asia Pacific 1998 3rd Quarter Translations from TV and Print (Box 1)
  - RL00734-OP-0607 through OP-0767: Bob Jeffrey DVD catalog (Box 1)
  - RL00734-OP-0726 through OP-0729 (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-001: AAAA (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-004: AICP Show, 2000 (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-005: Allen's Picks, 1998 (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-016 through UMATIC-017: Asia Pacific 1998 1st Quarter Review (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-062 through UMATIC-071: Detroit Weekly Reel (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-125: Hong Kong (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-127: Hong Kong (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-129: IBM (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-137 through UMATIC-138: Japan/Kellogg's (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-140: JWT/Ford (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-183: Mumbai (Hindustan Thompson) (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-252: Tokyo (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-272 through UMATIC-273: Worldwide Creative Council Benchmark Submissions, 2001 (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-280 through UMATIC-298: Video Strategies 1981 Guide (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-281: Video Strategies (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-285 through UMATIC-286: Video Strategies (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-287: Video Strategies (Box 1)
  - RL00734-UMATIC-301 through UMATIC-312: Video Strategies (Box 1)
  - RL00734-VHS-041: D&AD show reel (Box 1)
  - RL00734-VHS-047: Detroit/Ford (Box 1)
  - RL00734-VHS-050: Detroit/Allen Thomas (Box 1)
  - RL00734-VHS-053: Detroit/Cannes (Box 1)
  - RL00734-VHS-088 through VHS-089: Ford (Box 1)
  - RL00734-VHS-149: Thompson Total Branding (Box 1)
  - RL00734-VHS-153: U.S. Department of Justice/Drug Enforcement Administration (Box 1)
  - RL00734-VHS-154: U.S. Brewers Association (Box 1)
  - RL00734-VHS-156: Vietnam (Box 1)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Clark, Harry F. Jr., 1959-1993 (Box 1)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Connell, Hugh, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Cronin, Jack, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): De Angelo, Augusto, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Information from UNC, 1990-2003 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Johnston, Don, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Lanigan, Denis, 1990-1992 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Preschel, W. Lee, 1992-1995 (Box 2)
    Scope and Contents
    2 folders
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Robertson, Don, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Senior, Rai (Raimond del Noce), 1992-1994 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Sutton, Tom, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Swank, Cynthia, 1991-1995 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Thompson, Don, 1990-1992 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Transcription services, 1989-1999 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Varney, Norman, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Webster, Jack, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Oral History Project (Transcripts, releases, correspondence): Wilson, Edward B. (Ted), 1992 (Box 2)
- Audio Materials, 1953-2000; undated; 2
  - AAA radio, Undated (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-001)
  - Advertising Hall of Fame, 1979 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-002)
  - Alun Jones--New York Society of Business and Economics Writers, 1977 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-003)
  - American Hawaii Cruises radio :60, 1992 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-004)
  - American Personal Communications (APC) creative reel, 1996 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-005)
  - American Personal Communications (APC) TV "No Baloney", 1996 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-006)
  - ANCO 50/50 Co-op radio spots, Undated (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-007)
  - Arrowhead--City Noise, Undated (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-008)
  - Arrowhead--Gringuita, Comadre, 1986 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-009)
  - Australian radio advertising and mood set for The Mind's Eye, Melbourne, 1988 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-010)
  - Be A Part of the Heart of Detroit: The Four Tops, Do It in Detroit campaign song, Undated (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-011)
  - Be A Part of the Heart of Detroit: The Four Tops, Do It in Detroit campaign song, Undated (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-012)
  - Bible radio spot, 1990 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-013)
  - Boxing Helena radio promotion, 1993 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-014)
  - California State Lottery--Bonus Radio, 1995 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-015)
  - California State Lottery--California Pirates, 1995 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-015)
  - California State Lottery--Carnival Cruise radio Jeff Bolt/Tina Holland, 1994 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-016)
  - California State Lottery--Cheap Radio, 1993 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-017)
  - California State Lottery--Fun in the Sun and 7 other spots, Undated (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-018)
  - California State Lottery--Language Lessons/Iron Man, 1996 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-019)
  - California State Lottery--Mercy, Mercy, 1993 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-020)
  - California State Lottery--Mercy, Mercy, 1993 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-021)
  - California State Lottery--Tuba, 1994 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-022)
  - California State Lottery--Tuba Doable/Rocks, 1994 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-023)
  - California State Lottery--Whales/Still Flying, Undated (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-024)
  - California Tourism--California Bound, 1995 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-025)
  - Chase and Sanborn--100th Anniversary Comedy Gems, 1964 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-026)
  - Chase and Sanborn--101st Anniversary Fred Allen, 1965 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-027)
  - Chase and Sanborn--102nd Anniversary/40th Anniversary of NBC parts 3-4, 1966 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-028)
  - Chase and Sanborn--102nd Anniversary/40th Anniversary of NBC parts 1-2, 1966 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-029)
  - Chase and Sanborn/Kraft Music Hall/Lux Radio Theater, Undated (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-030)
  - Chatham Foods--Bernard Weisberg speech to employees 45:00, 1977 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-031)
  - Chevron/Ortho--Radio :30, 1993 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-032)
  - Chevron/Ortho--16 spots, 1992 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-033)
  - Chevron/Ortho--8 spots, 1992 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-034)
  - Chevron/Ortho--Southern strategy spots, 1992 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-035)
  - Chevron/Ortho--Spring Radio spots, 1992 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-036)
  - Chevron/Ortho--Spring Radio spots, Undated (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-037)
  - Clio Awards--1983 Winners category tape (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-038)
  - Clio Awards--1988-1989 Winners (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-039)
  - Clio Awards--1988-1989 Winners (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-040)
  - Clio Awards--1988-1989 Winners (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-041)
  - Conroy's--Wedding Spot, 1987 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-042)
  - Conroy's; Great Bear; H&T; Von's, 1987 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-043)
  - Del Taco--Alexander Graham Bell March radio, 1991 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-044)
  - Del Taco--Back to School Sale, 1991 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-045)
  - Del Taco--Bud, 1991 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-046)
  - Del Taco--Coolest Way, 1991 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-047)
  - Del Taco--Chicken Burrito July radio, 1991 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-048)
  - Del Taco--Really Hungry/Elephant, 1991 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-049)
  - Del Taco--Taking Gym, 1991 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-050)
  - Del Taco--The Right Stuffing, 1991 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-051)
  - Demo tape: Burger King/Detroit FDAF creative "Chartbusters" tie-in, 1987 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-052)
  - Demo tape: Burger King/Detroit FDAF creative "Chartbusters" tie-in, 1987 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-053)
  - Dick Orkin/Bert Berdis (Humor) Time Magazine radio spots, 1975 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-054)
  - D.J. Int. Ann. Rep., 1977 (Box A1, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-055)
  - Ford--Watching the Fords Go By, 1956 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-056)
  - FDAF--Music (Middle of the Road, Country, Rock), 1973 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-057)
  - FDAF Gallup New Mexico--spots in Navajo and Zuni languages, 1974 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-058)
  - Galileo Research Menopausal Study--Study Group 1 Seeking Suffers, 2006 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-059)
  - Galileo Research Menopausal Study--Study Group 2 Seeking Suffers, 2006 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-060)
  - Galileo Research Menopausal Study--Study Group 2 Seeking Suffers, 2006 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-061)
  - Galileo Research Menopausal Study--Study Group 3 Work Full Time, 2006 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-062)
  - Galileo Research Menopausal Study--Study Group 4 Doctors OB/GYN, 2006 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-063)
  - Galileo Research Menopausal Study--Study Group 4 Doctors OB/GYN, 2006 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-064)
  - Galileo Research Menopausal Study--Study Group 7 Work Full Time, 2006 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-065)
  - Galileo Research Menopausal Study--Study Group 7 Work Full Time, 2006 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-066)
  - Galileo Research Menopausal Study--Study Group 8 Doctors PCP/IM, 2006 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-067)
  - Galileo Research Menopausal Study--Study Group 8 Doctors PCP/IM, 2006 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-068)
  - Goodyear--G-Metric/Sweeps, Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-069)
  - Health Alliance Plan radio campaign, Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-070)
  - Health and Tennis (Bally)--Bal-l-l-l-l-l-lys Tampa, 1990 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-071)
  - Health and Tennis (Bally)--Bones, 1987 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-072)
  - Health and Tennis (Bally)--Desire Chicago Phase I, Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-073)
  - Health and Tennis (Bally)--Nervous Countdown, 1987 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-074)
  - Health and Tennis (Bally)--Six Million Dollar Body, 1987 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-075)
  - Health and Tennis (Bally)--Torture...Routine..., Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-076)
  - Humorous radio spots, Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-077)
  - ILR Advertising Awards (British), 1980 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-078)
  - Interview with Bill Ross, President JWT/West by John Higgins, 1978 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-079)
  - Interview with Bill Ross, Chicago, 1978 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-080)
  - Interview with George Richardson, retired Account Manager/Representative, 1986 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-081)
  - Interview with George Richardson, retired Account Manager/Representative, 1986 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-082)
  - Interview with George Richardson, retired Account Manager/Representative, 1986 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-083)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Board Meeting, 1986 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-084)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Christmas Chorus, 1966 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-085)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Christmas Chorus, 1966 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-086)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Christmas Chorus, 1966 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-087)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Copy Test on NPR, 1985 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-088)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Crystal Ball (copy of LP), 1961 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-089)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Speech Tape 1: Sam Meek speech at Yale 1 of 2, Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-090)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Speech Tape 1: Sam Meek speech at Yale 2 of 2, Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-091)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Speech Tape 2: Birthday messages to Sam Meek, 1980 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-092)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Speech Tape 3: Untitled, Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-093)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Speech Tape 4: Ken Hinks, Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-094)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Speech Tape 5: Eyes on Thompson, Bob Colwell "A Venusian View of Advertising", 1964 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-095)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Speech Tape 6: James Webb Young, Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-096)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Speech Tape 7: Dunham Summary, Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-097)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company--Stockholders Meeting, 1976 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-098)
  - Jenny Craig--10 radio spots, 1991 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-099)
  - Jenny Craig--Fall Special Hispanic tag, 1990 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-100)
  - Jenny Craig--Flashing Number 11, 1992 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-101)
  - Jenny Craig--Grandma's Boy/Yo Yo Dieter, Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-102)
  - Jenny Craig--Jennie Reynolds demo, 1989 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-103)
  - Jenny Craig--Final Weeks/Flexible Payment Plan, 1990 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-104)
  - Jenny Craig--Personal, 1991 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-105)
  - Jim Kennedy, 1984 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-106)
  - Jim Kennedy, Undated (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-107)
  - Jenny Craig--Flashing Number, 1992 (Box A2, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-108)
  - Jenny Craig--Now You Can Offer, 1990 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-109)
  - Kaiser Permanente--1992 GQGM campaign (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-110)
  - Kaiser Permanente--3 radio spots, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-111)
  - Kaiser Permanente--4 radio spots, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-112)
  - Kaiser Permanente--5 radio spots, 1986 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-113)
  - Kaiser Permanente--7 radio spots, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-114)
  - Kaiser Permanente--10 radio spots, 1993 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-115)
  - Kaiser Permanente--11 radio spots, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-116)
  - Kaiser Permanente--14 radio spots, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-117)
  - Kaiser Permanente--50 Years Ago, 1990 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-118)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Blindfold Hawaii, 1986 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-119)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Fresno Care/People Who Care, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-120)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Change/Ellie, 1987 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-121)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Cleaners, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-122)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Community (Dr. Jacobs)/Family (Dr. Samuels) Connecticut state empoloyees, 1993 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-123)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Dr. Who/Mumbo Jumbo/The Name, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-124)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Dr. Who state employees Hawaii, 1988 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-125)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Everything Texas, 1986 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-126)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Family/Arrival Hawaii, 1987 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-127)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Growing Better/The Beginning, 1986 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-128)
  - Kaiser Permanente--New on the Block/50 Years Ago, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-129)
  - Kaiser Permanente--People Who Care, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-130)
  - Kaiser Permanente--People Who Care Atlanta, 1990 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-131)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Radio 60s, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-132)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Radio 60s voicovers, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-133)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Right, Right, Right, 1990 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-134)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Small Town and 3 other spots, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-135)
  - Kaiser Permanente--Teacher/New Facility; Between Friends/Personal Physician, 1986 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-136)
  - Kraft--75th Anniversary Song, 1978 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-137)
  - Kraft--75th Anniversary Family Reunion (Excerpts), 1978 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-138)
  - Kraft--75th Anniversary Radio Special, 1978 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-139)
  - Kraft--75th Anniversary Show, 1978 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-140)
  - L.A. Cellular; Arrowhead; Health and Tennis; Phonemate, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-141)
  - Lansdowne--Dimension (Mingles), 1980 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-142)
  - Laymen's National Bible Association--Turn, Turn, Turn, 1991 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-143)
  - Laymen's National Bible Association--Turn, Turn, Turn, 1991 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-144)
  - Laymen's National Bible Association--Turn, Turn, Turn, 1991 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-145)
  - Lux Radio Theater--W.C. Fields/Poppy, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-146)
  - Mexicana Airlines--21 radio spots, 1992 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-147)
  - Mexicana Airlines--$99 Dreams, 1992 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-148)
  - Mexicana Airlines--$99 Dreams/$79 Dreams, 1992 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-149)
  - Mexicana Airlines--$99 Fare, 1991 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-150)
  - Mexicana Airlines--$99 Special Fare, 1991 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-151)
  - Mexicana Airlines--$99 Special Fare, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-152)
  - Mexicana Airlines--$99 Special Fare 12 radio spots, 1991 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-153)
  - Mexicana Airlines--Mexicana Breeze, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-154)
  - Mexicana Airlines--Crunch/Organized 14 spots, 1991 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-155)
  - Mexicana Airlines--Pupusas con curtido, 1992 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-156)
  - Mexicana Airlines--Pupusas con curtido, 1992 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-157)
  - Mexicana Airlines--Pupusas con curtido, 1992 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-158)
  - Mexicana Airlines--El Vuelo a Zacatecas Hispanic radio, 1992 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-159)
  - Mexicana Airlines--Pupusas con curtido/La Mejor Opcion, 1992 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-160)
  - Mexicana Airlines--Second Summer Weekend/Daylight Savings tied 10 spots, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-161)
  - Mexicana Airlines--Son of El Vuelo a Zacatecas, 1992 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-162)
  - Miscellaneous songs 1947-1982, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-163)